class Quiz:
    def __init__(self):
        self.quiz = [
    {
        "question": "Who scored the first goal of 2024/25 UEFA Conference League Final?",
        "options" : ['A. Enzo Fernandez', 'B. Biraghi', 'C. Abde Ezzalzouli', 'D. Ndiaye'],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the home stadium of Bayern Munchen called?",
        "options": ['A. Allianz Arena', 'B. Stamford Bridge', 'C. The Bianconerri', 'D. Red Lounge'],
        "answer" : 'A'
    },
    {
        "question" : "What is Ronaldo's highest base EA SPORTS card rating?",
        'options': ['A. 90', 'B. 95', 'C. 94', 'D. 91'],
        "answer" : 'C'
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city did Chelsea beat Arsenal Fc 4-1, in a UEFA Europa League final?",
        "options" : ['A. Istanbul', 'B. Prague', 'C. Baku', 'D. Seville'],
        'answer' : 'C'
    },
    {
        "question" : "When last did FC Barcelona win the UEFA Champions League?",
        "options" : ['A. 2006', 'B. 2017', 'C. 2020', 'D. 2015'],
        'answer' : "D"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Who has the second most assist recorded in football history?",
        "options" : ['A. Pele', 'B. Ferenc Puskas', 'C. Zinedine Zidane', 'D. Thomas Muller'],
        'answer' : "B"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which Nation has won the most FIFA World Cup?",
        "options" : ['A. Argentina', 'B. Germany', 'C. Brazil', 'D. France'],
        'answer' : "C"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Who scored the winning goal against Argentina in 2014 FIFA world cup final?",
        "options" : ['A. Pizarro', 'B. Mario Gotze', 'C. Arshavin', 'D. Mario Gomez'],
        'answer' : "B"
    },
    {
        "question" : "What is a poker in football terms?",
        "options" : ['A. Alternate for Hattrick', 'B. Brace', 'C. A Super Hattrick', 'D. 3 Assists'],
        'answer' : "C"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Who is the first Manager/Head Coach to have won the UEFA Conference League?",
        "options" : ['A. Jose Mourinho', 'B. David Moyes', 'C. Enzo Maresca', 'D. Sebastien Hoeneb'],
        "answer" : "A"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which Midfielder is the highest scoring midfielder in the English Premier league",
        "options" : ['A. Fabian Delph', 'B. Kevin De Bruyne', 'C. Ryan Giggs', 'D. Frank Lampard'],
        "answer" : "D"
    }
]
